https://sommerfeldtools.com/privacy-policy

Glu-Bot Glue Bottle
Trend Tool & Bit Cleaner/18oz.
Privacy Policy
Sommerfeld's Tools for Wood created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and security and it discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Sommerfeld Tools for Wood website.
Cookies
Our site uses a temporary "session" cookie to track your product selections and to transfer data from page to page. It is not written to any file stored on your computer, and it does not contain any personally identifiable information.
Personal Information
If needed, we may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address is used to help identify your shopping cart. Your IP address is not used to compile demographic or behavioral information, personal or otherwise.
Our website uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. Financial information that is collected is used only to bill the user for products and services. Your personal contact and financial information is not shared with any third party, unless required by law.
Sommerfeld's Tools for Wood occasionally uses use e-mail addresses acquired through the website for promotional mailings. Sommerfeld's Tools for Wood may alert previous customers of special promotions via e-mail. Recipients will have a clearly defined opportunity to opt-out of receiving these e-mail communications from us.
This site gives you options for removing your information from our database so that you do not receive future e-mail communications or print catalogs. You may also use these options to change, and/or modify information you have previously provided:
Email:          ml@sommerfeldtools.com
Address:  1408 Celebrity Drive
Remsen, Iowa 51050
Phone:      1-888-228-9268
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. The Sommerfeld's Tools for Wood website uses industry standard P.C.I. compliant technology to protect your personal information. All private information you submit will be encrypted before transmission. In addition, The Sommerfeld Tools for Wood server is updated with the latest security features and patches as they are made available.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can use our contact form or call us directly at 1-888-228-9268.
Company Information
About Us
Testimonials
Site Map
Account Information
Login / Register
View Cart
Privacy Policy
Sommerfeld Tools for Wood.
All Rights Reserved.
We Gladly Accept:
